A couple months ago, I interviewed one of
the richest self-made women in the entire world.
Excuse me, ma'am. Ma'am, question
for you. Is this your Bentley?
Yes, it is.
And what do you do for living out here
in Miami to be able to afford a Bentley?
I'm an entrepreneur, an investor.
How long have you been a business owner?
Oh my gosh. Well, I'm no longer really
a business owner. I sold it in 2023.
You sold a company?
I sold my company, yeah.
For how much?
For me, my equity shares were worth about $90 million.
$90 billion?
Yeah.
So how much was the total company sold for?
Well, the company was valued at
the time a little over $300 million.
That video got over 30 million views across social media.
That's Ann Malum.
And she sold her business and made
over $90 million in a single day.
She's got a $100 million net worth, you guys.
And I flew all the way out to
Miami to go to her house and interview her,
get the actual blueprint and the
secret to get rich in today's world.
So this video is about to
be insane from start to finish.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
All right, you guys.
So we're going to be linking up
with the nine-figure mogul Ann Malum very soon.
But before we do that, look, I'm in
one of the wealthiest parts of Miami right now
in the design district to go
around to find eight-figure, nine-figure billionaire entrepreneurs
to figure out how they created their wealth in
one of the richest cities in the entire world.
Let's go see who we can find out here.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Have a good day.
Ma'am.
Take care.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I know you.
Yeah?
I was 23.
Are you an entrepreneur?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
Six years now.
Do you think I can interview you
for a minute for the channel real quick?
Is that cool?
Yes, I would love to.
Let's do it.
Awesome.
What was the turning point to becoming an entrepreneur?
I left Saudi Arabia when I was 18.
My dad called me and he's like, I know
you're 18, but I can't send you money anymore because
his business was failing.
He was also an entrepreneur.
And when your back is against the
wall, you always end up figuring it out.
So I don't prey on anyone for their back
to be against the wall, but it is probably
the biggest blessing.
Like when you have no way out,
you make a way no matter what.
Did you hit rock bottom?
Yes, because I was literally 18 going to university.
I had to work two, three jobs to
provide for me and my family as 18.
For someone that lived in Saudi
where the culture is women don't work.
So suddenly I'm working all these jobs trying to
figure out why I had even a broken English.
So that's why I always tell women there's
no reason why you couldn't make it in this
life.
Broken English, background this, family this, whatever
your past is, take that, take all
the lessons and use it to
just make a lot of money.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
It will be this year.
How much?
We're on track to make 20
million me and my business partners.
Are you serious?
Yes.
20 million?
I know.
That's incredible.
How did you scale from a
one to a $10 million company?
The most important thing is hire people
that are better than you in your company.
Because I don't know it all.
And I know I don't know it all.
I'm not the smartest.
But you know what happens to the smartest people?
They're always the brokest.
Why?
Because smart people, they're overthinking, overanalyzing.
They need it to be perfect.
And when you want something to be
perfect, there's someone half your talent, half your
luck, half your intelligence already making
moves and making millions because they're
faster.
They're bolder.
They figure it out along the way.
Most people want to have
all the plan before they move.
Just move.
You will figure everything in the doing.
It's not in the thinking.
That's why they always say that the A
students always end up working for the C students.
I was a C student.
Did you have anybody that doubted you?
Everyone.
The Middle Eastern, like Middle Eastern women are
more like, you know, just have kids, sit
at home.
That was the culture that I was in.
Obedience is what I was taught my whole life.
Just be obedient.
Listen to the man.
Like your little voice, be quiet.
But the side of me that rebelled
is what made me successful and free.
So you're good at selling?
Oh.
If it's one thing to make you rich.
As a woman, sales, branding.
You will never be broke.
If you have a brand, you'll never be broke.
Everyone's literally throwing opportunities at you.
Like, please do this with me.
Please speak here.
Please sell this.
So give me a million dollars
worth of branding advice right here.
People are not nice anymore on social media.
They don't give chances anymore.
So if you want to blow up on social
media and you want people to respect you, two things.
Number one, they're not going to give you
a chance to make sure whatever you're saying
in the first three seconds is going to trigger them.
And sometimes that could be something positive
that you're going to say or negative.
But the hook, the first three
seconds is more important than the video.
You look at my Instagram reels.
The first three seconds is when people like.
They don't even watch the full video.
Then another thing is always giving perspective shifts.
If you're someone that says something that
is maybe controversial or maybe it's not the
normal or what people are used to listening.
If you give perspective shifts on why
you believe whatever you believe, people are going
to respect it.
Even if they don't believe it.
And then you can charge
high prices for whatever you're charging.
Some of the best branding advice that I
ever heard was that the best personal brands are
superheroes because they fundamentally
stand for and against something.
You have to be willing to die on that hill.
You have to make it.
You have to polarize.
Controversy is not a bad thing.
You have to be hated.
Look at the most successful people.
Elon Musk hated.
Trump hated.
Andrew Tate hated.
Kim Kardashian hated.
But then there is that other side that
people love them and adore them for whatever they
do.
Whether you like them or not, they're successful.
They're billionaires for a reason.
And they're not rich.
They're wealthy.
Yes.
The more heat you can get as an
entrepreneur, the more successful you're going to get.
If you don't want heat, you
don't want the people talking about you.
I think just working a job is nice.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
It was great to meet you.
So nice meeting you.
Keep crushing it.
One thing about you, your consistency is unheard of.
And I love that.
And I already know the billionaire status
is happening because people our age, they're
not doing it like that.
They're not consistent.
So I'm proud of you.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
You guys, we just ran into a 26-year-old multimillionaire
who's going to do $20 million this year at
her business.
She's from the Middle East.
Got her out here in Miami.
And she just gave a million dollars
worth of game during that entire interview.
Miami's going crazy right now.
We got to keep this one rolling
and go get another one, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, guys.
Excuse me.
Who's the richest person here?
Who's the richest what here?
How did you get rich?
I own one of the largest
tan salon franchises in the world.
What's that?
I own one of the largest
tan salon franchises in the world.
So you own tanning salons?
Yes, sir.
How many?
We're currently up to like 270.
So tanning salons made you rich?
Tanning salons made me wealthy, yes.
How wealthy?
What is your net worth?
I'll let you guess.
More than 10 million?
Over that, yeah.
A little over that.
More than 100 million?
Over 100 million dollars?
Yes.
So if you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Absolutely.
What would you do?
Honestly, if I lost everything and I had literally
no capital to start with, but I did have my
network, that's easy.
I'd go raise money and basically
do the same thing I'm doing now.
Which is what?
Commercial real estate and business.
Why tanning salons?
Of any business you could
have gotten into, why tanning salons?
I was 21, naive, a bunch of white girls
at the University of Arkansas where I was going
to school.
They always complained about tanning in Arkansas and
saying that it just wasn't up to par with
what was in Dallas.
So I saw a gap in the
market and decided to take advantage of it.
So how do you feel about haters?
Man, I don't pay attention to them.
I've never met anybody who's doing
better than me that hates on me.
As someone who's worth over 100 million.
What is the best financial advice
you could give to the younger generation?
I have a Rolls Royce.
You know what that stands for?
Rolls Royce?
Yeah.
What?
Recurring revenue.
Focus on recurring revenue.
Everything in our lives in the next 10
years, it's already shifted that way, but everything
in our lives in the next 10 years
is going to be on a recurring revenue model.
So from our car wash is on recurring revenue.
There's our dog food is on recurring revenue.
Our medicine, Netflix, gym, our tanning salon,
every single thing is on recurring revenue.
So focus on anything that
you can make recurring revenue from.
That's where the money's at.
What was the number one book that changed your life?
The E-Myth.
With the E-Myth, it talks about acting.
It's if you have 500
locations, even when you have one.
So we built systems and processes in place
for a long time before we ever expanded.
So whenever it came time
to expand, it was like that.
Do you think somebody should start
or buy a business in today's world?
I would buy a business, man.
The opportunity is there.
This thing called the Silver Tsunami, where
all these baby boomers are selling their business.
Their kids either don't want it or they don't
have kids that are in a position to be able
to take it.
And they want to retire.
So they want to sell their business.
There's so many businesses for sale and not enough buyers.
And a lot of these businesses are boring businesses.
So everybody wants to have a clothing brand.
Everybody wants to have a restaurant.
Those are not business.
Businesses are going to make you real money.
There's, you know, it's maybe 1% or less
than 1% are actually make real money from that.
But the business, the, you know, the pest
control guy, the HVAC company, all those people
are making real money and nobody wants those businesses.
So go find you a boring
business from somebody who's looking to retire.
You could probably even get preferable
financing through owner's financing and things like
that.
So even if you don't have money,
they'll still want to take the risk.
And that person is financing you.
So if you don't have money,
how exactly would you buy that business?
I would owner's finance it.
That's how I got my first business.
I owner's financed it.
I didn't have money.
How do you feel about AI?
I love AI.
I think that any person that wants to be
in the workforce in the next 10 years needs to
learn how to utilize AI.
Are you using AI in all your businesses?
Absolutely.
A lot of people are scared of AI because
they think that AI is going to replace the worker.
It's not going to replace the worker.
What AI is going to do is AI
is going to make the worker more efficient.
So essentially, if you needed 50 people to
run a certain department, you might only need
So it does make it more efficient, which therefore
does make it to where you need less workers.
But having a more highly skilled and more
effective workforce is ultimately going to be better
for everybody.
Have you seen this before?
No.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, yeah.
It's called Transcribe.
It's called Plot AI.
It records all the meetings, all the conversations.
I've never seen anything like it before.
It is insane.
Actually, I want one of those.
It's like a personal assistant, basically.
Yes.
No, it's game changing.
AI is insane.
I agree.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
I appreciate it.
So my guy got rich.
I mean, wealthy off of tanning salons.
But you saw that I had to show
him what we just got from Plot AI.
Guys, AI is the future.
And if you're not using it now
every day, you're going to get left behind.
And like I was telling him, guys, this thing
records all of my calls, all of my meetings,
and sends me a direct summary
right after and transcribes it perfectly.
See, taking notes during a meeting is a productivity killer.
You miss what's happening now because you're
too busy trying to just write everything down.
So it distracts you and makes you
less engaged with the people you're meeting with.
That's why I use Plot.
It's a sleek device that
literally takes my notes for me.
It's perfect for in-person meetings and doesn't drain
your phone battery if you're trying to record.
Plot has an app that gives you everything you need.
A full transcript, action items,
and smart summaries in minutes.
So there's no more.
There's no more scribbling.
There's no more.
Wait, what did they say again?
It's literally like having a second brain
that's organized, never distracted, and always on.
So if you're an entrepreneur, an executive, a
leader, or anyone who runs meetings and conversations,
this is your unfair advantage.
Don't just show up to meetings.
Start owning them.
So Hard Knocks family, click the link
below right now to have a look.
Use my code PLD22 and receive
a 22% discount for shopping season.
With that being said, let's get back to the video.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you get rich?
Hey, real quick, real quick for a woman.
Real quick for the younger generation.
That's a great podcast by the way.
Yeah?
I love what you do.
What's your name?
Mike Jagger.
And what line of business are you in?
Real estate developer.
Developer.
Commercial, residential.
What are you doing?
Industrial, multi-res.
Industrial.
Nobody talks about that.
Why is that such a good
business to get into right now?
Give me some game.
Listen, COVID, if anything, exploded the industrial market.
What happened during COVID, everybody's
getting packages delivered to their house.
Where do these packages come from?
Warehouses, right?
Distribution centers.
Yeah.
So that's something that I opened
up with my partner just before COVID.
September 2019.
So were you always really good at seeing
opportunities before everybody else got into the market?
I was working for a developer and my
partner was working for my direct competitor for about
10 years.
And we said, you know what?
Time to take a risk, go on our own.
Mortgaged everything we had, put it all into the business.
And fortunately for us, it was a great success.
So you weren't afraid of risk?
Everybody's a little bit afraid.
Yeah.
You just got to go for it.
But what's the biggest risk you took?
Was it going all in on the company?
Absolutely.
Mortgaged every last thing we had.
Our homes, credit lines, credit cards, put it all in.
Fortunately for us, it succeeded.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, man.
No.
I worked for my dad.
He was doing all right.
Went into real estate and
had to sell everything I had.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
So I'll tell you this.
We started the company in 2019.
Today, the company's worth a little over $4 billion.
Are you a billionaire?
I do all right.
So you're a billionaire.
I'm able to take care of my kids today.
Congratulations, man.
Thank you, man.
Really, really appreciate it.
You guys are doing a great job.
What is the secret to scaling out
to a billion dollar, multi-billion dollar company?
You know what?
Never be satisfied.
Keep taking risk.
Keep going for it.
Do you think entrepreneurs, the reason why
they struggle is because they get too comfortable
and everybody comes and gases them up?
You know, the one thing I suggest or the
one opinion I have, if you come from money, it's
probably a downfall.
You got to be willing to take risks.
You got to be willing to go forward.
You got to be willing to see opportunities.
And when you don't have anything, you have drive.
Did you ever have anybody that
doubted you when you were coming up?
Everybody, even family.
Leaving a stable job to risk it all
and to move into a one and a half.
I just got married.
My daughter was a month old.
Thought I was crazy.
So I think the biggest people doubt you
are the ones that are closest to you.
It's crazy how that works.
Absolutely.
And everybody wants you to
succeed, but never more than them.
That's what I see.
That's what I hear.
And then it's true.
Do you need a lot of
money to get into real estate today?
No.
You need to have people that believe in you.
You need to be able to take risks.
You have to have people with
the same vision as you do.
We found investors that understood what we're
aiming for and they believed in us.
You always got to think
what you can do for them.
You consider them like your own kids, your own family.
Make them a lot of money
and then they'll be behind you.
Now I need you to
give me a secret right here.
What's the best city to buy real
estate in today's world that nobody talks about?
So I'm from Canada.
I'm from Montreal, but I love Miami.
You like Miami?
We're looking for opportunities in Miami.
We're looking for opportunities.
Why?
Is it growing or what?
Population, right?
And with the multi-res business, we see
huge opportunities of people are going to be
fighting away from condos, from owning
to renting, just because of liquidity.
People don't have that much of it.
So you got to rent.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much.
This is a beautiful thing.
Congrats, man.
I really, really appreciate what you're doing.
I appreciate you, man.
Thank you so much.
Real quick, sir.
Is it possible?
Can I get your contact?
Is that okay?
Absolutely.
Awesome.
Guys, the time has now come.
We're about to go link up with one
of the richest self-made women in the entire world,
Ann Malum, who sold her company and made
$90 million in a single day to herself.
Not the business.
That's what she made in a single day.
Man figure business and how you can
get rich just like her in today's world.
Let's go link up with the business legend
and go see what she has to say.
All right, you guys, we just got to
Ann Malum's house out here in Miami, Florida.
And it's safe to say that she
lives at an absolute compound out here.
This is one of the craziest hopes
I've ever seen in my entire life.
But I'm going to be getting the exact secrets
from her on what it takes to really get rich
in today's world and build a company that's
able to sell for hundreds of millions of dollars.
So let's go meet up with her right now.
Ed, how's it going?
It's great to see you.
Good to see you.
This is Ruby.
What's up, Ruby?
How are you?
She has to check you out.
Good to see you.
Great to see you.
Thank you for having us back out here.
Yeah, thanks for coming out.
We had to do it again.
Okay.
That last interview, I was telling
them, got over 30 million views online.
That's amazing.
They loved it.
They loved you.
I mean, you made $90 million in one day.
It's true.
I mean, it's, you know, as you say, you get
like a wire one day, but that was nine and
a half years in the making.
Take us back to that day before
we get into the game right here.
What was that day like when you sold your company?
You made $100 million in a day off of that.
You know what?
Honestly, didn't feel.
It felt fake.
It felt real.
Like I knew that day was coming
and I knew the value that I created.
And so it felt like, yeah, this is my moment.
And I did what I
said I was going to do.
So it felt really like awesome.
I love it.
Now I have one rule for this interview.
Yeah.
No holding back.
We're going to give them the secrets on
what it takes to become wealthy in today's world.
Can we make that happen?
Yeah, we can do that.
I'll tell you everything I know.
I want everybody to be rich.
I always tell my friends I need them to
make more money so they can pay for shit.
Let's get right into it.
Who am I here with today?
Hi, I'm Anne Malum.
Nice to see you again, James.
And for those that don't know.
What was your business?
My business was Solidcore.
Talk to me about you were
a pioneer in the fitness boutique industry.
Where did that concept originate from?
How did you ultimately come up with this idea?
You know, I feel like both Solidcore and
Back of My Feet, the nonprofit I started,
I felt like my ability as an entrepreneur to
be successful was finding the things before people found them.
I'm not like crazy book smart.
Like I also need to be really passionate about something.
So when I tried a Pilates class, I
was like, oh, my God, nobody knows about this.
Nobody's built a big brand around this.
Nobody's built community.
Like that's what I know.
I know how to do.
So I felt like that's a game I can win.
And so getting in super
early, there was pros and cons.
Right.
The pros were I was in super early and
the cons were nobody knew how to explain this thing.
It wasn't really Pilates.
It wasn't strength training.
And so our tagline became this is
the hardest workout you never heard of.
So that got people interest.
They started coming in.
You were so sore the next day.
And so you had to go tell all your friends.
And we never spent a dime on marketing for the first four
years of Solidcore because people just had to tell everybody that they knew
about the business.
Were you ever afraid of competition?
No, everybody should be afraid of
me if I come in your space.
But like, I like to win.
Right.
So if I'm going to do something when I started
Solidcore, I never set out to do just one studio.
Like the first day I opened, I'm
like, I'm going to build an empire.
And even when COVID hit, it
was like, I'm here for it.
Like, I don't mind this challenge.
I don't know what this is, but this
pandemic virus isn't going to take this from me.
It was just figuring out what I needed to focus
on during that time to come out on the other side.
What was the one thing you did
differently from 99 percent of other entrepreneurs?
Well, I think I'll tell you two things.
One, I created a North Star.
So from the very beginning, I
knew what my end game was.
I was going to open 100 studios.
So when opportunities were coming up along the
way to franchise, someone wanted to buy my business.
When I had 10 studios, I was very
clear on what I was going out to do.
And so having that clear sight
of path, I never got distracted.
So that's one thing.
Two, I wanted it bad enough.
Like a lot of people want it,
but they don't want it bad enough.
And three, everybody always says, Oh my
God, Ann, you must have sacrificed so much.
And I really didn't feel like I sacrificed anything.
I loved it.
I loved building that company.
I loved creating a company that
was making people's lives happier and healthier.
So I was getting this positive
feedback loop on a consistent basis.
So if you're going to go into business
and be an entrepreneur, you have to find something
that fills you up, that you feel authentically connected
to, that you're going to want to work on it,
even through a two year pandemic.
Do you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
That may be controversial, but I don't.
I think all of the great entrepreneurs who really
make it right and you can start a business
and maybe, you know, have that for a few years.
I mean, the real entrepreneurs.
I think that they have something to prove.
I think they want to win
worse than anybody else out there.
And I think they have found something that
they feel is their footprint on the world.
Like building Solidcore and even building Back
on My Feet, the nonprofit, I felt like
I was enhancing people's lives and
that was really motivating for me.
Like if I was making desks or furniture
or something like that, I just wouldn't have
been a great entrepreneur.
Like it wasn't about the money for me.
It was always about the impact.
Knowing if I did a really good job and
created value for people, the payday would be there.
Was there somebody close to you that ever doubted you?
Yeah.
Was there somebody that ever doubted
you when you were coming up?
I mean, so many people, of course.
And I think people doubt you because they
love you and they want to protect you.
You know, they don't want to see you fail.
They want you to take a secure path.
Like when I started my nonprofit, right, this
wasn't to make money at all, but I didn't
I had a negative net worth and
I had to negotiate with my landlord.
I got my landlord to give me two months
free rent because I wanted to start this nonprofit
to help the homeless.
My dad was concerned for my safety.
Everybody was just like, this is
this is not going to work.
You know, like it's admirable that you want
to help people through this running club and
even solid core.
It's like 90% of gyms fail.
Like what are you doing?
You're making the wrong the wrong move.
So I do think people try to do it out
of protection, but it lands as like you're doubting, you're
doubting me.
And like I said, I didn't pick
things that weren't relevant to my skill sets.
It was lining the skill sets up with the business
that I felt I had the special sauce to really
make a big business out of it.
So you know, choosing something where you can
play a game that you can win, I think
is really a key component
of being successful in entrepreneurship.
Now you're worth over $100 million.
Where do you invest your money?
Where do the wealthiest people put their money?
Yeah, I mean, listen, I'm in wealth preservation
mode, not too much wealth creation mode, but
I still have a decent risk tolerance.
So I would say I have about 50% of
my money in public equities and I am an individual
stock picker.
Yes, I have ETFs, but I think
I have over $10 million of Nvidia.
Like I am in the AI game.
I need a secret right here.
What's the number one most underrated thing
nobody's talking about to get into right now?
I mean, listen, I still
think the AI game is early.
I think Palantir is early.
I still think Nvidia is early.
I mean, some of these.
Some of these people's have 2030 for
Nvidia being a stock price of $800.
It's $152 today.
Like I still think if you're not investing
in AI, you're going to look back and kick
yourself.
So I like public equities.
What do you mean by public equities?
Is that just like in the stock market?
Yeah, public company, right?
Public companies, right?
Anybody who has any money can go get
an account on a brokerage account like Fidelity.
I use UBS as my as advisors.
So I use their platform to buy and sell
stocks, although I don't sell very many of them.
So the thing about being wealthy that I'll
also share is once you have money, James,
you start to borrow and
use leverage for anything else, right?
So if I sell my stocks, I'm paying 20% if
I kept them for over a year, and that's better
than any kind of labor work from a
tax perspective, but I don't want to pay 20%.
So because I'm worth $100 million, UBS says, Hey,
and you know, you can have a $50 million
line of credit with us.
You can pull on it whenever you want.
Well, I also negotiated my margin rate because
I used to have my accounts with Goldman and
I left Goldman to go to UBS and I said,
but I want my margin rates to be lower than any
other client that you have.
And so I get to
borrow money at like $5 million.
Yeah.
Which is amazing.
So I would rather pay 5%
and sell my stocks and pay 20%.
I don't have to pay any
taxes on the money that I borrow.
So if I can see an investment that I
feel pretty confident that I'm going to make more
than 5%, if I'm going to make double digits,
I will borrow off the margin line and go make
an investment in a, in a startup or a
private company or loan somebody money at a 12 to
15% interest rate.
So it's safe to say that wealthy people,
they play a different game than everybody else.
Yeah.
And frankly it's a game that, you know, I
had negative net worth when I was 26, 27
and I hate when people say things like, I
just want to understand what is in my bank.
understand money or I never was taught that stuff.
Listen, man, either was I and a lot of other
people. And I think it's, you know, the only
person who loses when you decide not to learn
about money is you. Like read a book, listen
to a podcast. These things are available to absolutely
everybody. My nieces and nephews who are, you know,
20, 19 and 23, they have like 50 grand in
the stock market already. And they're constantly
asking questions and learning and trying to figure
out like how they can understand this game better
because they don't want to work their whole life
either. If you can instill one money
lesson into everybody around the world right now,
what would that be? Stop putting your money into a
bank. All the bank does is takes your money and
goes invest it in the stock market. They love
when people think that it's so secure to keep
your money in a savings account when you're making
less than, I don't know, a half a point
of interest on that. The bank says, thank you for
the free money. And now we're going to go invest
this in the stock market. So like you should have
very little in a bank. You should be putting it
into the stock market, whether it's index funds.
Again, if you don't know what that means, just
please read it.
And educate yourself because everybody can learn this
stuff and you have a much wealthy future in
front of you. And you know they don't teach
that in school, right? I know. Yeah. And listen,
capitalism doesn't work without a bottom. Wow. That's
a real game right there. Yeah. Do you
want to be in the bottom? I don't want to be
in the bottom. No, I don't. So give me another lesson
that the wealthy people do differently from
everybody else. Like what separates rich from
wealthy? I mean, listen, I feel like at this
point, like last week, for example, was a crazy
week in the market. You know, since April 7th, when
my account was at my low, I don't mind sharing
like what my account was. My account was like a
$40,000. I don't know what that was. I don't know
$39 million April 7th. My account is now back
up to $64 million in public equities alone. And
that's because the market is going to work its way
back up. And so sometimes I look at my account
and I'll be like, I just made like $1.2
million today. And I played volleyball most of the day.
Like when your money makes money for you, like
it wants to compound, it wants to procreate. And
even like the best text when I get from my
nephew of like, I made $2,400 in the market today. Like
that takes them two weeks to make that
if they're lucky at their age. So it's
really, really hard to make money. And I think
that's a really, really hard thing to do. And
realizing that you have to stack your assets and
you need to just let them continue to compound.
And I do, I feel like I'm cheating. One of
my values is generosity. Like when I have a great
month, like I'm giving away money, I'm making
donations, I'm taking my friends places. And I
think most importantly, I'm also just trying to
educate as many of my friends as possible that
like, I shouldn't have to pay for everything.
You should learn this game also. And it doesn't
matter if you're starting with $10,000, $1,000,
you got to start somewhere. And that's whether,
you know, losing weight, getting in shape,
like everybody has to have a day one.
Are you a good negotiator?
Yes, I'm a very good negotiator.
Give me your best negotiation
advice as a $100 million entrepreneur.
One, you have to make, I mean, read the
book, How to Win Friends and Influence People. I mentioned
that on the last one, right? But you have to
make people like you and you make people like you for
a few reasons. One, you say your name over and
over again, I'm going to give you great eye contact,
I'm going to make some jokes, and I'm going
to make you really excited about backing me. Because
again, I'm not like trying to get one by
you. I believe in myself more than anybody. And I'm,
it's my job to make you see that. So if
you're a landlord, and I'm trying to get you to say,
hey, let me like have first six months of
free rent, even though I've only been around business
for, you know, a year, I would talk about my
experience on back of my feet, I would get you
to come try a workout. Again, I wanted to meet you
in person so that you could look me in the eye,
and you could see my passion. So it's really
getting someone to like you and believe in you.
And that comes with a lot of confidence. So
I would just walk into any one of these meetings
and be able to articulate my vision and what I was
doing and why I was the right person to do it.
And your last message to the younger generation,
how can somebody become wealthy in today's world?
How can somebody get F?
You got to be an entrepreneur. So I'm gonna
say it again, you have to figure out what your
special thing is that you know how to do
better than like 95% of the population, right? And then
you've got to figure out how do I apply that
to a business that needs these skill sets and talents
in order for it to be successful. And lastly,
I do think you need to be super passionate about
whatever that business is, because there are days
that get long and boring. But like, if you're
excited about what you're building, you're not going to
want to quit and you have to enjoy the
process. It's not just about I mean, like I said,
I'm not going to quit. I'm going to enjoy the
process. I'm going to enjoy the experience. And I'm
going to enjoy the experience. And I'm going to
enjoy the experience. And I'm going to enjoy
the experience. And I'm going to enjoy the experience.
That day when I got that wire, that was exciting. But
what made it all worth it is I felt like I made
my money with pride and with integrity. And
I loved like the whole journey. It was really
rewarding. You got amazing advice. Yeah, thank you
so much for allowing us to come out.
Thanks. Good to see you guys and just went insane.
And this Miami video was one for the books. But I
need you guys to like and subscribe for
amazing content I've got coming every week because I'm
going all over the world to bring
you guys direct access to multimillionaire and billionaire
entrepreneurs. But here's the thing, it doesn't stop
there. See, I host live calls every week,
with the people that I interview, I literally
give you direct access to speak directly to these
people that I interview where you can ask
your questions to the people I interview and get
mentored from them every single week. It's the
number one community for business owners in the
entire world. And it's called the School of Mentors.
To join, all you have to do is go down
and click the link in the description of this
video. I can't wait to see you on the inside.
That being said, see you in the next video.